bytescout.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy Policy - ByteScout

Also see: [Cookie Settings](https://secure.bytescout.com/legal/cookie-settings)

**BYTESCOUT.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

**Last Updated** **October 4, 2018**

Thank you for visiting ByteScout.com, PDF.co, and/or one of our series of interconnected online applications available through one of the foregoing sites (collectively, sthe “Website”). We provide this Privacy Policy to explain how ByteScout collects, uses and shares information from you when you use the Websites and to help you make an informed decision as to whether to use or continue using the Websites.

  * ****Who controls my personal information?****

Any personal information provided to or gathered by ByteScout is controlled by:

ByteScout, Inc.   
1013 Centre Road, Ste. 403B   
Wilmington, Delaware 19805  
UNITED STATES

  * ****What information does ByteScout collect from me?****

The amount and type of information we gather depends upon your use of the Websites and, in some cases, what type of information you choose to disclose. We may collect the following information from you:

**Personal Information**

We collect information from you when you voluntarily register with ByteScout and/or submit your personal information to us over the Websites. Such personal information may include your name, email and postal addresses, phone number, product and/or subscription plan purchased, any customer identification number assigned to you by our payment processor, and other information which you voluntarily provide to us.

**Device/Internet Connection Information**

When you use the Websites, we automatically gather information made available by your web browser (such as Microsoft Edge or Google Chrome), Internet service provider (such as Comcast or Time Warner), and device (such as your computer, phone, or tablet), depending on your settings for each. For example, we may collect your IP address, information about the operating system or type of device you use, the date and time you access the Websites, and the location of your device. We may also collect information about your use of our applications, such as the date of activation. For example, if you use an electronic signature function in one of our applications, we may collect your IP address, location, device information, and the date and time of your electronic signature as a means of verifying the signature.

**Information Provided by Third Parties**

ByteScout may receive information about you and your Internet activities if you have provided it to a Third Party and we subsequently acquire the information from the Third Party. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your personal and online interests, and Internet browsing habits. These Third Parties may have collected such information by placing Cookies on your device, using web beacons, gathering IP addresses and log data, and so forth. The purpose of this practice, which is sometimes called “retargeting,” is to deliver content and advertising that is specific to your interests. For example, if you look at a particular product on the Websites, you may later see that same product advertised to you on Facebook. You can better learn about such Third-Party data collection and advertising practices, including how to opt-out of retargeting, at the following websites:

  * <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>
  * <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>
  * <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>

**Payment Information**

All payments are processed by third-party vendors, including MyCommerce, FastSpring and Stripe, and not ByteScout itself. If you make a purchase on the Websites, credit card numbers and related information, such as billing address, card number, and the expiration date of the card (“Credit Card Information”) is collected from you, but such information is sent directly from you to our payment processors through embeddable widgets and is never stored or otherwise retained by ByteScout.

**Other Information**

From time to time, we may obtain other information from you, such as when you make a claim for a prize pursuant to a contest or other promotion run on the Websites, when you request assistance through from our customer service department, and when you voluntarily subscribe to a ByteScout service or newsletter. You will always be asked to provide such other information voluntarily, and we will not collect it without your permission.

  * ****How does ByteScout use Cookies?****

“Cookies” are files that are placed on your device by websites you visit. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify you as a unique user of the Websites. A web beacon is programming code that can be used to, among other things, transfer an individual’s unique user identification (often in the form of a Cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows us to track certain websites you visit online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services you may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes.

We currently use Cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information we already have in our database, for the following purposes:

  * **_To Verify You._** We use Cookies to verify your account and make it so you do not have to reenter your login information each time you use the Websites.

  * **_To Analyze User Trends._** We also use Cookies for analytics and performance—that is, to gather information that helps us understand how you and other users engage with the Websites and our Third-Party partners and figure out how to do it better. The Third Party analytics vendors we work with include Google Analytics, MixPanel, Hotjar and Amplitude.

  * **_To Provide Support to You._** We also use Cookies, including those placed by Third Parties (including Zendesk, Drift, and Intercom) to provide customer support services.

  * **_To Advertise to You._** We also use Cookies and web beacons, including those placed by Third Parties, to deliver advertising that may be of interest to you. For example, we use the Facebook web beacon to better target and retarget users and potential users of the Websites by advertising to them on Facebook, Twitter, Quora, Google Analytics, Google Adwords, AddThis, and other Third Party Cookies may also be used in our advertising endeavors. We may also use a web beacon in email messages sent to track your response. Cookies and web beacons also help us and our Third-Party advertising partners ensure you do not see the same advertisements over and over and to identify block unwanted ads.

  * ****How does ByteScout use my information?****

We use the information we’ve gathered from you, including through Cookies and web beacons, for the following purposes:

**To Communicate with You**

We use information gathered on the Websites to personalize communication with you, and to respond to your requests for products, services, and information. By providing your email address to ByteScout through one of the Websites or related application, you consent to receive advertising emails from us. You can unsubscribe to advertising emails at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link within the email, or by contacting us at support@ByteScout.com. Please note that, even if you unsubscribe from advertising emails, we will still send you any necessary, non-promotional emails about your account or updates to our privacy policy and terms.

**To Improve the Websites**

ByteScout uses the information we collect from you and other users to provide and improve the Websites. As explained above, we use Cookies, including those placed by Third Parties, to gather statistical information that helps us understand how you and other users engage with the Websites and improve its performance.

**To Personalize Your User Experience**

We use information gathered from Cookies to determine whether you are logged in or not, and to allow you to set personal preferences when using the Websites.

**To Advertise to You**

As explained above, we use information gathered through Cookies and web beacons, including those placed by Third Parties, to deliver ads to you once you’ve left the Websites.

  * ****How does ByteScout share my information?****

**To Fulfill Your Orders**

We may transfer your information to Third Parties when necessary to provide a product or service that you order from us. For example, as explained above, your credit card information is provided directly to our processor through the Websites so that you can be charged (and we can be paid) for your purchase.

**To Advertise to Others**

We may share your reviews and comments about ByteScout to advertise and market our products and services. If you want us to stop using the personal data you have provided in these ways, please contact us at support@ByteScout.com.

**To Our Affiliated Companies**

We may disclose, transfer, and sell your information to our affiliated entities—that is, businesses that have common ownership with us—at our discretion, in which event, your information shall be treated by the affiliated entities in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Should ByteScout be subject to an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of control or business entity status, we reserve the right to transfer or assign your information as part of that acquisition, merger or sale.

**To Our Third-Party Partners**

We may disclose your personal information as needed to our Third-Party service providers and advertising partners. For example, we may share your email address with our email fulfillment provider. However, we will never sell your personal or non-personal data to any third party.

**To Comply with Legal Process and Prevent Harm**

We may disclose your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes. In rare circumstances, we may disclose personal information when we believe it is necessary in order to prevent illegal, fraudulent, or injurious actions that may cause harm to individuals.

  * ****How and where does ByteScout secure my information?****

ByteScout, and the Third Party vendors we use to store your information, employ security measures (such as SSL encryption and HTTPS protocol) to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your personal and commercial information, or other communications, will always remain secure.

ByteScout stores personal information in the United States. If you are visiting ByteScout.com from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States, and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using ByteScout.com you authorize and specifically consent to the transfer of personal information to the United States and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us.

  * ****How can I access or correct my information?****

You may access all information we’ve collected about you for purposes of correcting, amending, or deleting such information. Access can be obtained by contacting support@ByteScout.com. To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information to the Websites may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at support@ByteScout.com.

  * ****How does ByteScout protect the privacy of children?****

ByteScout will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. We have designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

  * ****Does ByteScout respond to Do Not Track (DNT) Signals?****

DNT is a feature offered by some browsers which, when enabled, sends a signal to websites to request that your browsing is not tracked. ByteScout does not currently respond to DNT requests.

  * ****What about Third Party practices?****

**Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons**

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, Third Parties) who place advertisements on the Websites and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Except as expressly provided herein, we do not control Third Parties’ use of such technology and we have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. It is up to you to familiarize yourself with the privacy practices of such Third Parties.

**Third Party  Links **

The Websites and email messages may contain hypertext links to the Websites of Third Parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. We do not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third-Party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

  * ****How will I find out about changes to the Privacy Policy?****

Each time you use the Websites, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Although most changes are likely to be minor, we reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy by posting such modification on this page; however, if changes are significant, we may provide a more prominent notice or email you. Unless we receive your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier version.
